<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Vacaville Real Estate Podcast with Andrew Lamb</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Andrew Lamb Team - your professional Vacaville Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Andrew Lamb</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-03-26 11:16:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Andrew Lamb</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Andrew@LambRealEstate.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Andrew Lamb</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Vacaville Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Andrew Lamb Team - your professional Vacaville Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcoming 2 New Members of the Team</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcoming-2-new-members-of-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-11 10:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/We+Have+Some+Exciting+Additions+To+Our+Team+-+Vacaville+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

As most of you know, we’ve been looking to fill a couple of roles here on our leadership team, the first being the broker of record. Well, I’m excited to let you know that we have identified our permanent broker of record! Currently, Pablo, our operating principle, is and will continue to be a designated Realtor—someone who can sign documents and act as a broker; however, we’ve always wanted someone local in the office to fill that role.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


With our recent addition, we’ve been able to do that. Kathy Luebke, who recently joined our office, is excited to start in her role of broker of record. Kathy has 33 years of real estate experience, having started in Solano County and then later opening an office of her own in Napa. Eventually, she sold that office and came back to Solano County.  Now that she’s joined us, all of her experience, growth, and leadership skills have come with her.

Many of you likely met her when she attended our first event BOLD last summer as a guest, which speaks to who she truly is: She’s all about our culture, eager to learn and grow, and she’s excited to support you in compliance and the growth of your sales business.

The next position we were looking to fill was that of a market center administrator, and we’re pleased to announce that we succeeded there, as well: Iris Cruz will be joining us as our new market center administrator.

“WE’RE VERY HAPPY TO HAVE FILLED THESE ROLES SO THAT WE CAN CONTINUE TO SUPPORT ALL OF OUR AGENTS AT AN EVEN HIGHER LEVEL THAN BEFORE.”

Iris has a degree in business administration and accounting. She was a staff accountant for four years before moving into a product specialist and technology role, in addition to being a certified trainer. With what we’re aiming to do with technology here at Keller Williams, she’s the perfect fit.

We are always building a bench, so if you have referrals for people who can fill those roles, we’d love to hear from them. In real estate, it’s good to have a couple of people in mind for depth positions, or positions that can be filled right away. If you know someone who would be interested in this opportunity, or if you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to us.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/We+Have+Some+Exciting+Additions+To+Our+Team+-+Vacaville+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/We+Have+Some+Exciting+Additions+To+Our+Team+-+Vacaville+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

As most of you know, we’ve been looking to fill a couple of roles here on our leadership team, the first being the broker of record. Well, I’m excited to let you know that we have identified our permanent broker of record! Currently, Pablo, our operating principle, is and will continue to be a designated Realtor—someone who can sign documents and act as a broker; however, we’ve always wanted someone local in the office to fill that role.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

As most of you know, we’ve been looking to fill a couple of roles here on our leadership team, the first being the broker of record. Well, I’m excited to let you know that we have identified our permanent broker of record! Currently, Pablo, our operating principle, is and will continue to be a designated Realtor—someone who can sign documents and act as a broker; however, we’ve always wanted someone local in the office to fill that role.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Get off the Real Estate Roller Coaster and Earn a Steady Income</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-off-real-estate-roller.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate Agent Tips</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2017-10-26 09:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/Five+Doors+And+The+Real+Estate+Roller+Coaster.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There comes a point where the volume of business you’re receiving becomes slightly difficult to manage.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


Trying to do a lot of business while simultaneously not being sure of who to hire to help you manage all of that business can put you on a real estate roller coaster, so to speak.

Imagine you’ve generated six leads, each with their own needs. Sometimes, servicing a number of leads at once can make it difficult to find the time to generate more. So, what happens when those six leads close?

At that point, you’re left at the bottom of the roller coaster. You go from six leads down to nothing instead of maintaining a constant stream of business.

When people try to balance lead generation with actually working with those leads, there is no time left for further lead generation and the whole process becomes inefficient.

One of the best ways to solve this problem is by joining a team—especially an expansion team. Doing this will give you more stability and leverage without sacrificing your income.

“JOINING AN EXPANSION TEAM LEADS TO MORE STABILITY AND LEVERAGE WITHOUT SACRIFICING INCOME.”

This is why expansion teams have become a core part of Keller Williams. An expansion team is able to handle the administrative process while agents do the footwork. Joining a team, especially an expansion team, leads to more stability and leverage without sacrificing income.

Expansion teams allow agents from across the country to work under a network of supportive, administrative staff that is in place so that they can focus on what they do best: helping clients to buy and sell homes.

Five Doors Network, the expansion team I’m part of, has 21 locations in 13 regions and as a result has been nominated for the 2017 Innovator Award for Most Innovative Team. But beyond that, there is simply a great level of financing available to put behind the core services.

At Five Doors Network, we put $2.1 million back into our hub so that we can better our services for clients and agents alike.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/Five+Doors+And+The+Real+Estate+Roller+Coaster.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/Five+Doors+And+The+Real+Estate+Roller+Coaster.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

There comes a point where the volume of business you’re receiving becomes slightly difficult to manage.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

There comes a point where the volume of business you’re receiving becomes slightly difficult to manage.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Guarantee Your New Hire Is Productive From Day One</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-guarantee-your-new-hire-is.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate Agent Tips</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2017-08-30 14:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How can you make sure your new hire is productive right away? Follow our three-part strategy.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


Today I’m going to teach you how to guarantee that your new hire is productive from day one. You might be surprised to know that it’s not a difficult process. It comes down to following three steps:

1. Define their 20%. This is in reference to the 80-20 rule which states that 20% of dollar-producing activities make up 80% of your revenue. These activities include prospecting, lead follow-up, going on appointments, negotiating contracts, and practicing scripts. We ask our agents to do these things from day one because we want them to start making contacts right away.

2. Create a path with milestones. There should be a checklist for your new hire to follow every step of the way so they know what success looks like from the start.

3. Check in daily and set up specific 30, 60, and 90-day checkpoints. At each checkpoint, we make sure our new hires have completed their lists. They either did or they didn’t, so there’s no debate about whether they are on the path to success or not. A new agent on our team, Hannah, did a great job at hitting her goals by simply following our playbook and taking off.

If you have any questions for me at all, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

How can you make sure your new hire is productive right away? Follow our three-part strategy.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

How can you make sure your new hire is productive right away? Follow our three-part strategy.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Is an Expansion Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-is-expansion-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Career Opportunity</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2017-08-01 09:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/What+Is+An+Expansion+Team%253F+-+Vacaville+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Expansion teams are real estate’s new frontier. They provide more opportunities for agents and clients alike.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


Today I’m here to bring you some information about expansion teams, and how you can know whether they are something that could be right for you.

So, how is an expansion team different from a local real estate team? An expansion team is, essentially, a local team that has kept all of their core, or hub, services in one location, but finds sales agents in other markets.

For example, while I’m located in Vacaville, California, it isn’t at all uncommon for me to receive leads from other nearby markets like Napa.

Even though Napa is only about a 30-minute drive from Vacaville, a majority of real estate agents simply don’t want to commute. They also, oftentimes, feel uncomfortable working in a market they maybe don’t know as well as their immediate, local area. When this is the case, those agents usually refer the clients to a Napa agent instead.

“EXPANSION TEAMS ARE THE NEW FRONTIER OF REAL ESTATE.”

The issue with this, though, is that eventually all those referrals add up to a lot of lost potential business. This is where the concept of an expansion team comes in.

Instead of referring clients out, a team receiving a lot of potential business from a given area might choose to hire an agent living in that area to do some of the footwork. And, because all of the administrative support is already taken care of, being an agent in this position can be a great opportunity.

So rather than just taking a 25% split for the referral fee, the way profit is shared can be negotiated within the team. Expansion teams, overall, are much more profitable as a business.

At Keller Williams, we’ve created a platform and a system that supports agents looking to expand their teams. Kristan Cole, the vice president of expansion with Keller Williams, has also come up with a lot of great tools and systems that will help agents launch into expansion.

This is a new frontier for real estate. It isn’t uncommon for businesses like Walmart or Costco, to expand, but the expansion of real estate teams is a relatively new thing.

If you have any other questions about expansion teams or our current real estate market, just give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/What+Is+An+Expansion+Team%253F+-+Vacaville+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/What+Is+An+Expansion+Team%253F+-+Vacaville+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Expansion teams are real estate’s new frontier. They provide more opportunities for agents and clients alike.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Expansion teams are real estate’s new frontier. They provide more opportunities for agents and clients alike.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our Team Is Growing</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/our-team-is-growing.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2017-03-15 13:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/Our+Team+Is+Growing+-+Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Our team is growing and we need help. We’re looking to add some new agents to help us take care of all the leads we have coming in each day.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


Our team is growing here in Vacaville and we’re looking to add some new members. If you are a licensed agent in the area who is looking to double your business and take your career to the next level, we want to hear from you. Even if you only sold three homes last year, we can help. We have taken agents from three deals a year to upwards of 30 within 12 months.

We are looking for hard-working, growth-minded individuals to come join our team and work within our systems and models to double, triple, even quadruple their production. We want everyone on our team to be selling 30+ homes per year. We have way too many leads to handle and we need help.

We have a full-time transaction coordinator, a full-time listing manager, and all the support you could possibly need as an agent. We will even help you set appointments to fill up your calendar so you can meet with buyers and sellers to accomplish their goals and in turn, accomplish yours.

“WE WANT EVERYONE ON OUR TEAM TO SELL 30+ HOMES EVERY YEAR.”

If you’re interested, let us know. You can give me a call, send me an email, or click the link below to schedule a meeting on my calendar so we can talk about this opportunity and how it can benefit you.

Click here to schedule a time to meet with me

If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to reach out. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/Our+Team+Is+Growing+-+Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Video/Recruiting+Videos/2017/Our+Team+Is+Growing+-+Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Our team is growing and we need help. We’re looking to add some new agents to help us take care of all the leads we have coming in each day.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Our team is growing and we need help. We’re looking to add some new agents to help us take care of all the leads we have coming in each day.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>90 Listings in 90 Days Is Tomorrow! </title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/90-listings-in-90-days-is-tomorrow.html</link>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2016-04-06 15:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I wanted to take a moment to invite you to a great event we have coming up, 90 Listings in 90 Days. It couldn’t be more timely, as the spring market is starting to heat up! The buyers are out and looking for homes, but we’re short on inventory. As an agent, this makes your job more difficult.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


“YOU DON’T WANT TO MISS THIS FANTASTIC EDUCATIONAL OPPORTUNITY.”

That’s where Craig Reger comes in. He’s been selling real estate in Portland for more than 17 years, and he wants to share how he took his inventory from zero to 90 in only 90 days. The event is April 7, 8:30am, at Travis Credit Union. You don’t want to miss this great opportunity to learn how to become a more productive agent.

If you have any questions about the event, please don’t hesitate to reach to us. We’re always here to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

I wanted to take a moment to invite you to a great event we have coming up, 90 Listings in 90 Days. It couldn’t be more timely, as the spring market is starting to heat up! The buyers are out and looking for homes, but we’re short on inventory. As an agent, this makes your job more difficult.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

I wanted to take a moment to invite you to a great event we have coming up, 90 Listings in 90 Days. It couldn’t be more timely, as the spring market is starting to heat up! The buyers are out and looking for homes, but we’re short on inventory. As an agent, this makes your job more difficult.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Stay Busy During the Holidays?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-stay-busy-during-holidays.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate Agent Tips</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2015-12-04 13:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+Staying+busy+now+is+important+for+next+year.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today we’re talking about how you can stay busy during the holiday season to ensure you have a great start to 2016. At the end of the year, real estate tends to slow down in general across the country.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


However, it doesn’t really happen that way in Northern California. Just last November, we had 6 closings. There are buyers and sellers out there, but not as many agents. The truth is that it’s the agents that slow down as opposed to the market.

The number one tip I have for you in order to have a good start to 2016 is to start getting everything under contract now, so you will see that money when the new year starts. Make sure you are following up on leads and calling past clients, this is a great time to dig in and show them you are working hard at a time of year when many aren’t. They will appreciate that.

“This is a great time to ask for referrals!”

Another thing you can do this time of year to really impress your clients is to hold a client appreciation event. We hold a free pie giveaway at our office and invite all our past clients and spheres to come and grab a free pie (which we get for $6 a piece at Costco) to show we are thinking about them and thankful for their business. This is a great referral tool.

As for how we keep busy within our team, we like to do a contest around this time of year called a “Go for no,” where you go out and ask as many people as you can, in person, whether you know them or not, and if they know anyone looking to buy or sell a home in the next year. The fear of asking this question is what keeps most people from getting referrals, and you’d be surprised about the answers you’ll get. It’s not about them saying yes, it’s about asking the question and being comfortable with them saying no.

Now is a great time to really build up those client relationships, spread your joy, and ask for referrals. If you have any questions for us or want to talk about what we do on our team to generate business this time of year, please feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We would love to speak with you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+Staying+busy+now+is+important+for+next+year.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+Staying+busy+now+is+important+for+next+year.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today we’re talking about how you can stay busy during the holiday season to ensure you have a great start to 2016. At the end of the year, real estate tends to slow down in general across the country.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today we’re talking about how you can stay busy during the holiday season to ensure you have a great start to 2016. At the end of the year, real estate tends to slow down in general across the country.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Do Our Raving Fans Have to Say?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-do-our-raving-fans-have-to-say.html</link>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2015-09-23 16:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Today I’m going to answer one of the most frequent questions we are asked: “How do we recruit raving fans in our business?” We have so many repeat and referral customers that continue to spread the word about our company, we wanted to share with you some of the strategies that have led us to get where we are out. Basically, it comes down to delivering a great customer experience and maintaining good relationships. We’ve got three key points to focus on today, here they are:


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


1. Decide what you want your customer experience to be, and define it.

For us, it’s very clear that our sellers want a proven, repeatable system to sell their home for up to 18% more than traditional methods. It’s a clear system that follows clear strategies. The same is pretty true for buyers, who want that proven, repeatable system that can save them tens of thousands in unnecessary costs.

2. You’ve got to know your customer and what they want.

We have specific client experiences we want to have with our buyers and sellers, and we have specific programs catered to each client. Every one of them is thinking “What’s in it for me?” so it’s our job to show them. When we approach how we want to interact with these people, it’s always about what’s in it for them, which is determined by knowing who they inherently are. We tailored all of our systems with our clients around these.

3. Deliver, plus one.

This is a phrase we like to use around here and it basically means going that extra step or extra mile for the client. Something that puts their experience over the top, like providing a free home warranty.

When you add all of these elements together, that’s what creates a raving fan, who will refer business without being asked and be your biggest cheerleader when it comes to growing your business. We strive to create that Disney-like feel with our customers, and we want to be a place where people want to come buy and sell homes.

If you have any questions for us about our raving fans or about our business in general, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today I’m going to answer one of the most frequent questions we are asked: “How do we recruit raving fans in our business?” We have so many repeat and referral customers that continue to spread the word about our company, we wanted to share with you some of the strategies that have led us to get where we are out. Basically, it comes down to delivering a great customer experience and maintaining good relationships. We’ve got three key points to focus on today, here they are:

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today I’m going to answer one of the most frequent questions we are asked: “How do we recruit raving fans in our business?” We have so many repeat and referral customers that continue to spread the word about our company, we wanted to share with you some of the strategies that have led us to get where we are out. Basically, it comes down to delivering a great customer experience and maintaining good relationships. We’ve got three key points to focus on today, here they are:

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>10 Things Every New Agent Needs to Know</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/10-things-every-new-agent-needs-to-know.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Career Opportunity</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2015-08-03 11:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+10+things+I+wish+I+knew+when+I+got+licensed.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today, I cover 10 things I wish I knew when I first got my real estate license. If you’re a new agent, or an agent who is still trying to become a top producer, you might find these tips helpful. Let’s jump right in:

“These are simple and easy tips to remember!”

1. I wish I knew to focus my time on P-L-A-N. This means Prospecting, Lead generation/followup, Appointments, and Negotiation. These are the only things in real estate that make you money, so focusing on them first thing every morning will help a lot.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


2. About 20% of the activities you do every day lead to 80% of your results, meaning money in your pocket.

3. Don’t believe everything you hear, especially when other agents say they’re doing what works for them. Just know that most agents don’t track their results and may think something is working even if it’s actually costing them money.

4. Master effective scripts and dialogues. Don’t be afraid to role play, because practice makes perfect. Make sure you are only saying what you need to say and practicing that with someone else before talking to live leads. Make sure you have it down before you go out and talk to potential clients.

5. Develop lender relationships and leverage those relationships like crazy. Some of the biggest and best referral sources are other business owners in town. Whether it’s lenders, appraisers, or handymen, teaming up with professionals around town can really help your business!

6. Forget farming and brand advertising. All you really need to do is put out some kind of landing page or direct response marketing and get people to respond to an offer that actually brings value to them and puts them first. No one cares about who you are and why they should work with you; they just want to know what’s in it for them! Focus on getting your information in front of someone and making an offer they can respond to.

7. Go deep and not wide with your marketing. So many agents end up spreading themselves too thin and get no results. Make sure you’re investing your time and money into a few things that are going to work consistently, rather than testing 100 things and never getting true consistency or results from any of them.

8. Find a mentor, whether that means driving an hour to meet with one of the top producers in the area or paying a coach for real estate related advice that’s personalized to your business. Find someone to learn from and copy their success. Real estate is really a pretty simple business, you just need to find someone who demonstrates results and profit every single year.

9. Real estate as a practice is not a business. You are now a business owner. You can’t just come in to the office whenever you want or work without a purpose. You truly are responsible for doing dollar-producing activities and following up and tracking the results and numbers of your business. In other words, run your business like a business and you are sure to have success.

. Do not chase squirrels. Do not get distracted by all the phone calls you recieve from sales people and from all the ads targeting you trying to sell you shiny new objects to help your business. If you keep jumping from product to product, it’s a surefire way to waste all of your money and get no results. You really just need to focus on a few key things and you will get the best results.

These are simple and easy tips to remember - I just wish I knew them when I first got my license. If some of these tips are new to you, or if you’re having trouble implementing some of these ideas in your own business, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’m always available to chat and share advice on how you can grow your business!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+10+things+I+wish+I+knew+when+I+got+licensed.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+10+things+I+wish+I+knew+when+I+got+licensed.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today, I cover 10 things I wish I knew when I first got my real estate license. If you’re a new agent, or an agent who is still trying to become a top producer, you might find these tips helpful. Let’s jump right in:

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today, I cover 10 things I wish I knew when I first got my real estate license. If you’re a new agent, or an agent who is still trying to become a top producer, you might find these tips helpful. Let’s jump right in:

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Building Your CRM Using Your Sphere of Influence</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/building-your-crm-using-your-sphere-of.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Career Opportunity</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2015-07-23 09:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+Tips+for+fledgling+real+estate+agents.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you’re starting out as a new agent, you need to utilize your sphere of influence. You need to figure out the 50-100 people that you’re comfortable asking if they know anyone that’s looking to buy or sell a home. Starting from there is easy, because it’s not difficult to convince people that you know to work with you.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


I always tell new agents to start playing a game called, Who Do I Know? You can look in a variety of places to begin this search.

Who do you know from past jobs? Who do you know from school? Look for people that you’ve shared experiences with, and find people that would be willing to help you.

“Who do you know that I should know?”

This leads me to the next big question, which should be aimed at the people you’re talking to. Ask them who they know that you should also know. This could be someone they know that simply has a shared interest. It doesn’t need to be someone that’s looking to buy or sell a home or someone who works with real estate.

It’s also beneficial to ask them about contractors that they know because they own a home. These people make a living off of people buying and selling homes, and they are a good source of information on potential clients.

These people don’t have to be friends, they can be acquaintances or just people that you run into at the grocery store.

Once you do have these 50-100 people, you need to put them in a contact relationship management system (CRM) so that you can continue to reach out to them in the future.

This is a great way for new agents to start building out contacts. If you have any questions about this, please don’t hesitate to contact me!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+Tips+for+fledgling+real+estate+agents.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+Tips+for+fledgling+real+estate+agents.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you’re starting out as a new agent, you need to utilize your sphere of influence. You need to figure out the 50-100 people that you’re comfortable asking if they know anyone that’s looking to buy or sell a home. Starting from there is easy, because it’s not difficult to convince people that you know to work with you.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you’re starting out as a new agent, you need to utilize your sphere of influence. You need to figure out the 50-100 people that you’re comfortable asking if they know anyone that’s looking to buy or sell a home. Starting from there is easy, because it’s not difficult to convince people that you know to work with you.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What's the Secret to Productivity?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-secret-to-productivity.html</link>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2015-06-03 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+The+key+to+productivity.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today, I just want to share a helpful tip that I use every day to help me be more successful. One thing I’ve noticed among successful people is those who really manage their time well seem to be the most successful. One thing I try to do each year is manage my calendar and manage my time, and to do that, I use something called the Dominate Your Day planner.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


The goal of the Dominate Your Day planner is to free up time for you to do more dollar-producing activities. You need to prioritize activities that will generate business and get you closings so that you’re not constantly reacting to the chaos that is the real estate transaction.

One cool thing about the Dominate Your Day sheet is it has a three-project focus that helps you determine what you’re going to put your mind to throughout the week. If you accomplish those three things, you should be much closer to the goals you set at the beginning of the month or the beginning of the quarter.

“The Dominate Your Day planner will change your life.”

You can also divide each day in 6 Must Do MONEY MAKING Activities. The first two are typically the things that bring in the most money, like bringing in new business or prospecting. The bottom four can be anything from negotiating a price reduction to setting followup appointments for people you’re still trying to find homes for. Really, this part of the planner is for anything that gets us into contract or closer to a closing. Things like responding to emails or scheduling inspections should be done later in the day.

It’s crucial to focus on the hardest things to do at the beginning of the day, while you have the most energy. You don’t want to be interrupted by the whims of others, so it’s very important to time block these important activities. The little things that aren’t necessarily dollar-producing can be listed at the bottom of the Dominate Your Day planner under the Action Item List.

The last thing to look at on the sheet is the Positive Focus…Go B-I-G or go home! section. This is an area where you can record your wins for the day. It’s easy to get overwhelmed or bummed over a long day, so it’s important to record every win you have throughout the day, every positive thing that happens to you.

If you would like a copy of this incredibly helpful planner, give me a call at (707) 301.8694. I would love to hear from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+The+key+to+productivity.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+The+key+to+productivity.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today, I just want to share a helpful tip that I use every day to help me be more successful. One thing I’ve noticed among successful people is those who really manage their time well seem to be the most successful. One thing I try to do each year is manage my calendar and manage my time, and to do that, I use something called the Dominate Your Day planner.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today, I just want to share a helpful tip that I use every day to help me be more successful. One thing I’ve noticed among successful people is those who really manage their time well seem to be the most successful. One thing I try to do each year is manage my calendar and manage my time, and to do that, I use something called the Dominate Your Day planner.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Do You Have What it Takes to Succeed With Our Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/do-you-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed.html</link>
        
          <category>Northern California Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Career Opportunity</category>
        
        <author>Andrew Lamb</author>
        <pubDate>2015-05-22 09:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+The+fast-track+to+real+estate+success.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Hey everyone, today we are very excited to announce a few brand new open positions with our team. Right now, we are looking for four qualified buyer’s agents to join our team, as well as an executive assistant.


Thinking about a career in Northern California real estate sales?
Email me today for a private real estate career consultation.


Our team has been growing rapidly and we have too many leads to handle on our own, so we are looking for four buyer’s agents to service all of these leads. We have a 30-day fast start program, where we will get you caught up to speed on our company and teach you how we conduct business successfully. We expect all of our buyer’s agents to succeed with our systems and expect them to make six figures. In fact, we guarantee that you will make at least $60,000 in your first year working with us as an agent, and if you don’t, we will pay you the difference.

The other position we are looking to fill is for an executive assistant. We want someone who can really help us manage and support our team to the best of our abilities. We are looking for someone who can make sure the schedule is all taken care of.

If either of these positions sounds like an ideal fit for you or somebody you know, please give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to helping you advance your career!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+The+fast-track+to+real+estate+success.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Andrew+Lamb/Northern+California+Real+Estate+Agent-+The+fast-track+to+real+estate+success.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Hey everyone, today we are very excited to announce a few brand new open positions with our team. Right now, we are looking for four qualified buyer’s agents to join our team, as well as an executive assistant.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Andrew Lamb</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Hey everyone, today we are very excited to announce a few brand new open positions with our team. Right now, we are looking for four qualified buyer’s agents to join our team, as well as an executive assistant.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Vacaville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Andrew Lamb</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Andrew Lamb</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Andrew Lamb Team - your professional Vacaville Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
